Guide to the Kenneth M. Cuthbertson Papers SC0582
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Kenneth M. Cuthbertson Papers
1941-1990
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Cuthbertson, Kenneth M.
SC0582
76 Linear Feet (125 boxes)
The papers, which include correspondence, minutes, reports, and memoranda, pertain largely to administration, finance, and planning at Stanford University. Specific subjects include the PACE campaign, the Campaign for Stanford, the libraries, the Medical School, student housing and fraternities, the Near West campus as proposed in the 1980s, the Centennial Campaign, admissions, football, and affirmative action.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The papers were received via administrative transfer, 2000-2001.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Kenneth M. Cuthbertson graduated Phi Beta Kappa from Stanford in 1940 and returned after his wartime service in the Navy to earn his MBA in 1947. After seven years in the business world, he returned to Stanford in 1954 as assistant to university president J. E. Wallace Sterling. Cuthbertson was named one of the university's first three vice presidents in 1960. With Sterling and Provost Fred Terman, Cuthbertson helped to define Stanford's goals of attracting top faculty, developing programs to meet their needs and finding endowment support. He organized the two largest fund-raising campaigns in the history of American higher education, the PACE (Plan of Action for a Challenging Era) campaign of 1961-64 and the $300 million Campaign for Stanford, which set another new national benchmark in 1972-77. Following his retirement from Stanford in 1977, Cuthbertson served as president of the James Irvine Foundation in San Francisco and Irvine, Calif. He died in 2000.
Description of the Collection
These papers, which include correspondence, minutes, reports, and memoranda, pertain largely to administration, finance, and planning at Stanford University. Specific subjects include the PACE campaign, the Campaign for Stanford, the libraries, the Medical School, student housing and fraternities, the Near West campus as proposed in the 1980s, the Centennial Campaign, admissions, football, and affirmative action.
Universities and colleges -- Administration.; Universities and colleges -- Business management; Cuthbertson, Kenneth M.; Cuthbertson, Kenneth M.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2000-021
  - "A" (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - American Tel and Tel (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annenberg, Walter H. (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Arbuckle, Ernest (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ayer, William E. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Ba - Bi" (Box 1, Folder 11-16)
  - "Ba - Bi" (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Babb, Phillip S. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bailey, Arthur E. (Box 2, Folder 4-6)
  - Bechtel, Kenneth K. (Box 2, Folder 7-10)
  - Bechtel, Stephen D. (Box 2, Folder 11-14)
  - Beckman, Arnold (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Berry, Lowell (Box 2, Folder 16-20)
  - Berry, Lowell (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bing, Peter (Box 3, Folder 3-5)
  - "Bl - Bp" (Box 3, Folder 6-11)
  - "Br - Bz" (Box 3, Folder 12-19)
  - Blume, John A. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Boswell, James G. (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - Boys Town (Box 4, Folder 3-6)
  - Bravo, Francisco, M.D. (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
  - No Title (Box 4, Folder 10-13)
  - Briggs, Reid (Box 4, Folder 14-15)
  - Brinton, William (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Brown, Alden (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Brown Foundation (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Robert Minge (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Browning, Matt (Bobbie) (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
  - Buckley Administration (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Burvis, Joseph J. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ca-Cd (Box 5, Folder 7-10)
  - Ce-Cl (Box 5, Folder 11-14)
  - Co-Cz (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Co-Cz (Box 6, Folder 1-5)
  - California Educational Facilities (Revenues, Bonds--CEFA) (Box 6, Folder 6-8)
  - Cal-Tech (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - California, U. of (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Camp, James J. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cantor, B. Gerald (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
  - Cantor, B. Gerald (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Carlson, Allison (Box 7, Folder 3-5)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Chamberlain, Ross (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Chandler-Times Mirror 1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Chandler-Times Mirror 1973-74 (Box 7, Folder 9-12)
  - Chandler-Times Mirror 1971-72 (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
  - Chandler-Times Mirror 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Chicago University (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Children's Hospital at Stanford (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Children's Hospital Medical Center Foundation (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Chinese companies (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chrysler Corporation (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Clark, Edna McConnell Foundation (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Clever, Linda Hawes (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cogswell, Elinor (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Columbia University (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - CCSU Committee for Corporate Support (Box 8, Folder 13-15)
  - Corbus, William (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cowell Foundation (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Criley, A. E. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Crocker, William (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
  - Crown Family (Box 9, Folder 5-7)
  - Cully, Grant B. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - "D" (Box 9, Folder 9-13)
  - "D" (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Danforth Foundation (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Davis, Arthur Vinning Foundation (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Davies, Ralph K (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Davis, Paul H. (Box 10, Folder 5-7)
  - Davison Family (Nelson Bernie) (Athbasca Ranch) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Dee, Thomas (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - DeGurrre Funds (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Dickinson, Farleigh (Box 10, Folder 11-12)
  - Dillingham Corporation (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Djerassi, Carl (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Dreyfus Foundation (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
  - Drown, Joseph W. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Eastman Kodak Company (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Eberle, William D. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Educational Foundation, Inc. (Swigart, Ted) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Elliot, John E. Brick (Box 11, Folder 3-5)
  - ESO Education Foundation (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Exxon (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "F" (Box 11, Folder 8-14)
  - "F" (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Fairchild Foundation (Box 12, Folder 3-8)
  - Fleischmann Foundation (Box 12, Folder 9-15)
  - Fleischmann Foundation (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Fluor Corporation (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - FMC Corporation (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 13, Folder 4-9)
  - Ford Motor Company (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
  - Frye, Clayton "Wes" (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Fuller, W. Parmer III (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - "G" (Box 13, Folder 14-17)
  - "G" (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
  - Gallo Family (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Gannett Foundation (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Gardner, John W. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Gates Foundation (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Gilmore Commercial and Savings Bank (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Ginzton, Edward (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Goodan, Mrs. Roger (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Gore, Mrs. Thomas (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Graham, Katherine (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Green, Cecil H. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Green, Cecil H. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Grube, Karl P. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - "Ha - Ho" (Box 15, Folder 5-8)
  - "He" (Box 15, Folder 9-11)
  - "Hi - Hz" (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - "Hi - Hz" (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - Haas, Peter (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Haas, Walter (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
  - Halaby, Najeeb (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Hanna, Paul (incl. Folder on Honeycomb House) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Harvard (Box 16, Folder 10-12)
  - Hatch, Mrs. George C. "Gene" (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Hawes, Payton, Mrs. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Heller Family (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Hettinger, Albert J. (Box 17, Folder 3-7)
  - Hilgard Fund (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Hoagland, Henry W. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Hodgson, Richard W. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Hoffman, Eric (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - "I" (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
  - IBM Corporation (Box 17, Folder 14-16)
  - Irvine Foundation (Box 18, Folder 1-6)
  - "J" (Box 18, Folder 7-11)
  - Japanese Universities (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Robert Wood Foundation (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Thomas V. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Japanese Companies (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Japanese Companies (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
  - "K" (Box 19, Folder 6-10)
  - Kaiser Family Foundation (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Kaiser Family Foundation (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - Kates, Arthur (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Kauffman, Virgil (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Kenan, William R. Trust (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Killefer, Tom (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Kimball, William R. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Klein, Robert (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
  - Koenig Report (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Koshland, Daniel (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Kratter, Martin (Box 20, Folder 13-15)
  - Kratter, Martin (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Kresge Foundation (Box 21, Folder 2-6)
  - "L" (Box 21, Folder 7-11)
  - Lancaster, John (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Land, Edwin H. (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
  - Lane Family (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Leckie, William H. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Lee, Russell V. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Levin, Adam and family (Box 22, Folder 7-9)
  - Levinson, Robert (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, Roger (Box 22, Folder 11-12)
  - Lilly Foundation (Box 22, Folder 13-14)
  - Lowenstein, Allard (Box 22, Folder 15-16)
  - Luce Foundation (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Lurie, Robert (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - "Mac/Mc," general (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - "Mac/Mc," general (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
  - McCarthy Foundation (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - McCloskey, Paul N. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - McCoy, Bowen H. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - McCreery estate (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
  - McCurdy, Richard (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - McDermott, Eugene (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Maguire, Jack (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Marcus, Ellen (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Markie Foundation (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Marx, Lawrence, Jr. (Box 23, Folder 14-15)
  - "Ma-Me", general (Box 23, Folder 16-18)
  - "Ma-Me", general (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
  - Mellon, Andrew W. Foundation (Box 24, Folder 3-7)
  - Mellon, Richard K. Foundation (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - "Mi," general (Box 24, Folder 9-14)
  - "Mo - Mz," general (Box 24, Folder 15-19)
  - Merrill, Fred H. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Merrill (Chas) Trust (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
  - Middle East (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Harold A. (Box 25, Folder 5-8)
  - Mobil Oil Company (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Montgomery, Kenneth F. (Harle Garth Damann) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Moore, Robert S. Fund (Box 25, Folder 11-13)
  - Morrison, Dean (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Mount Kisco Meeting (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Munro, William B. Fund (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Munzer, Rudy J. (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Murdock Trust (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Myers, Anna Laura (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - "N" (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - "N" (Box 26, Folder 1-5)
  - Napier, Davie (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 26, Folder 7-9)
  - National Distillers (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - New Founders League (Box 26, Folder 12-17)
  - Newhouse Foundation Scholarship (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 1907 Foundation (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - "O" (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
  - Occidental Petroleum Corporation (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Olin Foundation (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
  - "Pa - Pe" (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
  - "Pe - Pg" (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - "Ph - Pz" (Box 27, Folder 11-12)
  - Pacific Medical Center (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Co. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Pauley, Edwin W. Foundation (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
  - Pelissero, Godwin (Canfield Foundation) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Pacific Gas and Electric Co. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania, University of (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Sloss, Louis / Margaret (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Sloss, Eleanor / Leon (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Spaeth, Carl b. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Spencer Foundation (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Oil / California (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Oil / Indiana (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Children's Convalescent Hospital (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Stanford research (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Stauffer, John (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Stern, Lucie Trust 1975-74 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Stern, Lucie Trust 1973-71 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Stewart, Ruth (Mrs. Dwight) (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
  - Stone Foundation (W. Clement/ Jessie V.) (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Storke, Thomas (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Sutro, Robert (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Syntex (1of 2) (Box 29, Folder 10-11)
  - Sweeney, Stender/ Robert, Dean (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Symonds, Gardner (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - System Development Foundation (Tyler) (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - "T" (Box 30, Folder 2-7)
  - Tanner Foundation Meeting (Wednesday 4/13 9a.m.) (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Tanner, Obert C. (Box 30, Folder 9-12)
  - Thomas, Joseph M. (Box 30, Folder 13-15)
  - Timken, William R. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - TRW, Inc. (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - "U" (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - U.S. Steel (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - "V" (Box 31, Folder 4-6)
  - Varian Associates (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
  - "W" (Box 31, Folder 9-17)
  - "W" (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
  - Weeden, Alan (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Wente, Karl (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Winds of Freedom (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Hoover Institution (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Human Biology (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Humanities and Sciences - Linguistics (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Humanities and Sciences (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - International Studies (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Jasper Ridge (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Journalism (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Law School (Box 33, Folder 7-10)
  - Legal Services - Staff (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Library Prospects (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Library Groundbreaking (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Wohlford, Mary Burnet C. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - "X-Y-Z" (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Xerox (Box 34, Folder 5-6)
  - Yale University (Box 34, Folder 7-9)
  - Academic Council (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Academic Reporting (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Academic Reserve (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Physics / Applied Physics (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Art Department (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Augsburger, Robert (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Department (Box 35, Folder 3-4)
  - Bechtel Center (Box 35, Folder 5-6)
  - Behavioral Science (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Chemistry (Box 35, Folder 8-10)
  - Classics Dept. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Communications, Dept. of (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Computer Science (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Students (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Earth Sciences (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Economics, Dept. of (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Cowell Health Center (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Engineering Building (Terman) (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - School of Education (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Engineering 1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Engineering 1970-72 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Fire and Police Station (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - General Secretary (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Office of Foreign Visitors (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School of Business 1973 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Division (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - GSB fundraising meeting June 17, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 37, Folder 5-6)
  - Libraries (Box 37, Folder 7-10)
  - Libraries (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Libraries 1973 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Libraries 1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Libraries 1969-71 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Massy, William F. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Medical School (Box 38, Folder 6-8)
  - Medical School (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Medical School 1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Medical School 1971 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Medical School 1972 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Medical School 1974 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Church (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
  - S.U.M.C. Analysis of Hardware Alternatives for the Medical Center Computing Facility Feb. 1973 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Museum (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Music Department (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - New York Office (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Other Universities (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Overseas Campus (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Planning Office (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Political Science - 50th Anniversary Celebration (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Primate Center (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Performing Arts, Center for (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Professional Journalism Program (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Public Events (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Research and Development Center (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Outdoor Primate Facility "Gombe West". A statement prepared by Dr. Jane van Lawick-Goodall, ca. 1973. (4 copies) (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Values, Technology and Society Program (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Proceedings: 32d Annual Meeting of the Western Association of College and University Business Officers, April 26-29, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - SLAC Coordinating Committee (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Staff meetings - presidential (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Staff meetings (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Provost (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Office of Public Events (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - V.P. for research (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Campus security (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Peace Studies - Synergy (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - SLAC - audit reports (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Southern California Office (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University Hospital (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Structured Liberal Education (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Seven Universities Group (Box 41, Folder 14-16)
  - Seven Universities Group (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - Summer Conferences and Workshops (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Studies (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - University Fellows (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - University Press (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - University Relations (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Educational Staff Seminar 1973 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University Statistical Profile 1940-1970 [financial] (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Banks general (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Budget Adjustment Program (Box 42, Folder 11-13)
  - Bequests / Family and Charitable Intervivo (Comparison of) (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Borrowing, outside (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 1977-78 Compensation Proposal (Fall, 1976) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Operating Budget Guidelines 1975-76 (Box 43, Folder 3-5)
  - Budgets 1977-78 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Budgets 1976-77 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Budgets 1975-76 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Budget G.S.O (Box 43, Folder 9-11)
  - Budgets 1975-74 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Budgets 1975-74 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Budgets 1973-74 (Box 44, Folder 2-4)
  - Budgets 1972-73 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Budgets 1971-72 (Box 44, Folder 6-10)
  - Budgets 1971-70 (Box 44, Folder 11-12)
  - Budgets 1969-70 (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - Budgets Meetings RFB (Box 45, Folder 3-7)
  - Budgeting, Long-Range Forecasting and Budget Modeling (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Conflict of Interest (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Corporations - Stock Options (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Cost Studies (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Debt Policy (Recommended for Stanford University) (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Endowment Investment (Box 45, Folder 13-14)
  - Endowment Investment (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
  - Endowment for Innovation (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Expendable Funds Pool (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Facilities Planning (Box 46, Folder 5-9)
  - Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1976-1981 (Box 46, Folder 10-11)
  - Financial Analysis by Schools (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Financial Equilibrium (Massy) (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Annual Financial Report (Box 47, Folder 2-5)
  - "Facilities Plan and Capital Funding Forecast 1977-1982," April 1977 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Finance and Development (Box 47, Folder 7-10)
  - Assorted reports and documents (long range financial planning for S.U.) (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Assorted reports and documents (long range financial planning for S.U.) (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
  - Forecasts (Box 48, Folder 4-7)
  - Forecasts (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Funds Pending (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - G.P.I. Programs (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Gift Acknowledgement Procedures (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Gift Archiving (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Gifts - Analysis of Past Growth (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Gifts of Land and Property (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Land Resources Office (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Non-Monetary Gifts (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Gift Opportunities (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Gifts with a Preference (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Gift Procurement Program (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Gifts and Bequests 1920-1970, 50 Colleges (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Gifts - Historical Analysis 1961-1973 (J.A. 3/73) (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Gifts and Non Governmental Grants Received (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Gifts/Buildings (Prospects) (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Gift Procurement Cost Analysis (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Gift Restrictions Policy (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Gifts of Stock (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Gifts/Trustees (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Gifts Unrestricted (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Restricted Gifts (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Gifts/Pledges 1976 $1000+ (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Gifts, Expendable $100 million or more - Redesignation (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Largest Campaign Gifts (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Goals for Program (Activity Goals) (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Gripe List (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Insurance Reports (Box 50, Folder 11-12)
  - Investment Management (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Investment Responsibility (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Leases Prepaid (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Life Income Trusts (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Merged Fund (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Personnel - Administrative (Box 50, Folder 18-19)
  - Personnel - Administrative (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Annual Reports (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Benefits (Box 51, Folder 3-5)
  - Proposed Plan for Retirement Contributions (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Personnel - Emeritus (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Personnel - Faculty (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Personnel - G.S.O. (Box 51, Folder 9-12)
  - Personnel - Grievance policy (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Personnel - Strikes (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Pooled Income Fund Gifts (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Property, Appreciated (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Trusts with other Trustees (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Unitrust / Annuity: Trust gifts (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Yield and Gain Pool (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Cabinet (Box 52, Folder 7-11)
  - Trustees: Membership manual guide (Box 52, Folder 12-14)
  - Trustees: Membership manual guide (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - Agenda Review (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Finance and Development (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Agenda Trustee Reminders (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Trustees' Executive Session (CONFIDENTIAL) (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Office of V.P. / Business and finance. R. R. Augsburger (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Miller, William F., Provost (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Council 1972-73 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Dean's Council 1971 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Council of Deans of Schools (Pitzer) (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Reports - Special to Pres. Lyman (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Reports - annual to the President by KMC (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - V. P. Meeting (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth S. Lyman (Mrs. Richard) "Jing" (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Lyman, Richard W. (Box 54, Folder 4-6)
  - V. P. meetings 1975 (Box 54, Folder 7-9)
  - V. P. meetings 1974 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - V. P. meetings 1974 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
  - V. P. meeting Apr. 4, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - V.P. meeting Mar. 18, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - V. P. meetings 1973 (Box 55, Folder 5-6)
  - Visiting Committees (Box 55, Folder 7-8)
  - Visiting Committees (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Faculty/Staff housing (Box 56, Folder 2-4)
  - Eligibility for campus housing (Box 56, Folder 5-6)
  - Emeriti housing (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Low cost housing (Box 56, Folder 8-9)
  - Newhouse Foundation Finance Committee (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Newhouse Foundation Finance Committee (Box 57, Folder 1-5)
  - Newhouse Foundation 1976 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Newhouse (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Newhouse Foundation Finance Committee 1976 (Box 57, Folder 8-9)
  - Newhouse Foundation Finance Committee 1976 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Newhouse Foundation Finance Committee meeting agenda (Box 58, Folder 2)